Tell me how you think I'm wrong When I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think you're love You erase all that it cost
Tell me why you look at me Like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know When I give away my trust
One second, okay, can you guys hear me? Okay. Hi guys. What's up guys? Oh my god. It's just a stressful night. Oh my god
I don't know. I can't even get how you have horrible the night is. Oh
Hopefully you guys are okay
It's just me being like dumb and like doing it like friggin ain't like
Just being so dumb and like, you know
Like one thing after the other like it's like, you know
I don't even want to throw it to it, but it's just terrible
Oh
I'll be okay. I'll be okay
How are you guys?
It's like I'll say I can tell you what happened. It was just like very quiet. Hey, look at God. Hey, what's up?
Halo Haitian now. Hey, hello. Hey, Jamie
Hey everybody
Well
You anyway happen
It's just embarrassing now at this point. It's just embarrassing. Okay, so you know
I have this bike right and my neighbor it was like, you know for like they moved away
But they're like, you know, he's like, oh he bought the bet he bought the new battery for it and like
So yeah, so today like yes finally the bike in the war it worked
There was all fully charged like that he fixed it like he fixed the battery
Yes, I forgot that I had the stupid lock. Hi prairie. I had this stupid bike lock like
around the one of the spokes of the bike,
and then I started riding, and then all of a sudden,
the wheel lost it, the feeling of the wheel,
the pedals didn't have the tension anymore.
The lock is completely tangled up in the spokes
and the gears and shit like that, it won't come out,
it can't open it right now.
And then it's like the neighbors out of town,
but I mean, he knows how to fix it,
like I think he will be able to fix it,
it's just like,
You know, I have to ask him to come back and like fix the like shit and it's embarrassing
So then I was all stressed out and I'm out of cigarettes right now. It's like oh my god
So like if I like a I thought I had like 10 bucks on my card and then like I had like a few dollars
You know like dollars dollar bills and like some change
And so I went to the liquor store and I was like gave them the dollar bills and change and then I was like
I have like 11 dollars on my card. I was buying a few drinks and like a couple cigars and then
But then I like charge or charge the car the cars not going through and then he's like well
I can't cancel it now because
You have this cash in it. It was just being at all confusing. There's big line for me
I just let everyone in the line go the guy's getting really mad. I'm like, okay
Well, you know, he's like so I'm not giving you to go home and get the money
I'm like, I don't have the money at that. I thought I had it on the card. I just checked the big patterns, right?
And it was like there and so then
So I was like, okay, so I took you're trying to like take out one anyway
He eventually let me walk away with like one because I had like $5 or $5 should he sense cash or whatever
He let me walk away with one lemonade and one cigar
But he said I'm banned from the store. I don't know if I'll be banned, but he said I'm banned from the store
He was all mad and like, you know, it was like just a difference of like, you know, if you said I was like
I'll leave my driver's license. He'll bring it tomorrow. It's like, you know, but
Tomorrow, I mean I'll be able to tomorrow. It's just like it how everything happens like stressful because they get so stressed right?
From the bike thing and it's like all bluster from that and then it's like I need a cigarette and I'm out of
I'm out of it. I like get all my change. I'm like great
I had everything like sorted out, but I like I don't know like charges sometimes go through the last minute
You need to call someone if that happens. I know I didn't have I don't have anyone to call. I don't I
mean, it's like
I mean, it's like I could call my family. It'd be like this embarrassing to call anybody, right? It'd be like, oh, look at he's not
So anyway
Just stressful. Oh, yeah, well, I just think the whole story, you know, it's the bike top wearing mascara
Joe you're gonna
Maybe maybe oh, I think that's it. We don't reset me Friday
I don't know maybe because I think shows sometimes it's like they trolling me saying. Oh, yeah. I
Want to get a reading. I don't know if you do that you'll love it if you do have everyone
Hey, spunky hi guys, so I'm sorry like I hate being like a
Bad mood, but I hear I'm here look at I got this really cool shirt. You like my shirt. I should
That's fine for capricorn if you don't know this capricorn the curse is working good luck on that buddy
Oh, the curse though the Emma Leviathan curse. Well, I hear she's sick. Did you take the day off yesterday?
So maybe she's cursed. I'm thinking of that. I'm totally healthy. I'm just like having a little bit of bad luck. I
Think the worst curse is health
But I do wish she gets better. I bet you do with it, right?
You're playing Mario with Dingle. It was amazing time. Yep. Thank you so much. Yeah, I'd like this shirt, too
I got I'm getting a I'm getting a lot of new shirts on
You know
Timo don't say her name
Fred Alastair, I can say anybody's name. I want it's called freedom of speech called being American
What are you where we live against in a in some like, you know?
Fascist country or something. I'm not allowed to say names somebody's name. Tell me why
Can't say somebody's name. I'm not allowed to say is my defaming my doing defamation. Am I slandering am I?
Saying anything, but I'm not allowed to say somebody's name
So a public figure 25,000 subscribers by the way 25,000 subscribers, right or more, right?
She's 25,000 subscribers and she's on a public channel, but I'm not allowed to say is anybody else not allowed to say her name
Or just me I'm the one person in the world not allowed to say somebody's name. I just want to get it clear
I'm not allowed to say her name. Okay, first of all say who like who said that?
And who's gonna enforce that?
I wanna know exactly.
Strike, she's still crashing up.
You know who's gonna crash out of this chat?
Is this guy, Bean Gang, who's just a pain in the butt.
And I should have kicked him out the first day,
but it's like, you know, I was like,
oh, he's a Mexican guy, I like Mexicans, but.
I can make an exception.
Oh, I'll cry, I'll cry, bye, bye, never see you again.
That's the last thing you're gonna say on my show,
at least while I can handle it.
My mama, Vicky, what's up, we're all good.
So guys, if it's only does wanna sponsor the panel,
it would just take a little load off of me tonight.
But here, there we go.
Huh.
Cuz I'm like and then I'm like I'm like really like I
Were like what if
There's gonna be some like freak thing where the bike can't be like you won't be able to do it
He's been able to do it like past twice two times
You know it's like I know you should be able to do it, but then it's like it's like I'm like
Oh, you know I'm just saying they're worrying like the whole time before that. Hi. I'm on the deep
But you know what I'm feeling better it's like whatever if I need to like
She brought you a Halloween shirt.
By the way, why is Fred Alastair still here, by the way, too?
He will be hidden from now on.
I'll never see a bitch about Emma again.
If you guys see anybody come in and sit and talk talking like him,
like, oh, you're not allowed to say Emma's name, blah, blah,
just can you just hide that person?
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Moz.
Jamie's Cowboy Lava.
Mom of the Slucky Mokey.
Thank you. All right, babe. Hi. Um, Dingo, why aren't you with mod? Hold on. Dingo. Thank
you yesterday. Um, anybody else? Hi, babe. Hi, babe. Hi, babe.
Oh, you're kissing me. Kissing me, Katrina. Okay, I think we got everybody that should
be a mod. Here's a mod. You're welcome. Okay.
Yeah, I think I'm getting a better idea of who should be a mod or not like it's like, you know
But the mods, you know like mods by the way, it's like all yeah
You post links now, but just like phone views it and don't they don't know of course like you know
If it's like your link or something like somebody in the chat like you know go ahead and post any time
You know, but you know, I didn't like we had somebody like posting docs and stuff and I don't want that kind of stuff
Right. This is Lenore. This is just Lenore
She's like my little
Hi
You're the star
Some sugar Lenore. Oh
It's expensive some ass sometimes
Hi, where's the tricks is right up back. He's watching look. Are you watching tricks? You see you saw Lenore Christian
They know I already took boils away. I gave him one like one day
It was not like 10 minutes that he was saying inappropriate mod things. I
Know, you know, and I was like, you know
Let's spunky hold the rest of the wrench for the couple, but I can't hit him going rogue
Trust I trust Bunky with it. I don't know about just I know it's like I trust him with like, you know
Be a good like, you know a good boyfriend and stuff like that. I just don't know if he'll he'd be a good mod
I need to be so much care. I mean God. He was a mod until last night. He was God
He was the mod for a long time. I mean, it's like but then he had then he you know called like the guests of honor like
You know bad names like you know really
I kind of really said something's terrible like you know, it's like a
This like
That shit in it or the other one I don't want to say fat
But it's like, you know, same thing making remarks about somebody's weight
It's not appropriate. I mean especially like again, but you know what's funny. It was like Canada dry
JT, Gotti, LD, Ray, like, I was like, okay, I had like five people that I brought up and
every single one of them said something like really rude, really rude.
I was like what the fuck is they what is the point my audio is trash well random guy
Well, thanks for letting me know because they can always fix it
You know I have other audience first
You can say hey check your audience trash, you know, it's like like it's like oh
Good audio right right random guy now like you're helping me out with it right you're just gonna tell me my audience trash
You have no solution. You just want to talk shit. It's okay
Hey, yeah, whoever sends more to the cash up in one minute, and then he sends like been one minute. He sends one dollar
Like I'm like up like because he was expecting me
He's like and it was a test to see like if I go crazy over a dollar or something like that
Yeah
Yeah, oh Sam and you should see what people are doing like, you know, and then these are my mom my mods were like in here
I had a guest here, like a really nice lady, she's a shaman, she has a channel, she's
like super, like, you know, brave to be out there in the first place, because you know,
we all have insecurities about going on and doing a show and being out in front of people,
and it's like, and then it's like, but we kind of like, you know, expect some troll
sometimes.
Can you imagine if I would I mean I get trolled sometimes by the chat like the chat right but it's like
Not by like and sometimes good people that come on and stuff that it just seems like it's like I'm I'm maybe deserved to be trolled
Like she did not she didn't do anything like in there like people are like, oh, what do you think?
You know, you know this and this is this is that I mean it's like it is kind of like a metaphysical show where it's like
Yeah, some of this stuff is metaphysical. There's not gonna be oh, it's like scientifically proven
Whatever scientifically proven means the science is just a bunch of theories and like, you know human human beings trying to put things in like a
Understandable format, you know theory or you know, there's not very many proven 100% right?
So you get trolled by autistic people and they beat me. Okay, random guy. Well, yeah
Because you know what but first of all, why are you like making remarks about autistic people and how do you know?
I'm not autistic. I mean have it like why would you like throw around people like a inborn mental mental
State of mind with like something that's wrong with somebody. Why would you shame somebody for autism? I want to know that or
Shame somebody that's not autistic brought it up. What are you saying? He's really funny Vicky. You think it's funny Vicky?
Well, that's why you're not a mod, okay?
Okay, oh, hold on
Everything's this funny everyone thinks it's funny. Okay
Everyone thinks it's funny. Oh, that's what's funny. Oh, you're getting beaten by a random science isn't proven
That's why it's called the theory of evolution
You know the first time I was in a physics class in high school
The first thing the physics teacher said which is something common physics teachers will say is that physics is bullshit
You're not shaming autistic people why you're saying that I'm you know, even me, you know
Autistic people, you know, they can't beat anybody, but they can beat you right so you are shaming them, right?
because you're saying that
Well, it's like even like or you're trying to shame me or something, right?
You're trying to shame me if but you inadvertently now you've now you've
Now you've a disparity its higher Autism community
I would love on the autism community just to you know get a little clip of you know what you're saying about autistic people
You know, you shouldn't be really be saying those things, you know, the new climate. Okay, don't shame you don't shame people random guy
Okay
Yeah
No, they're not going to they're gonna they're gonna fucking troll me harder and random guys. I don't care random guy
I donated a million dollars. I'll still kick his ass out of here. I
Don't care. I just on the mood right now
But like you're my last nerve random guy. Let's just go ahead and test it
What did you see he's not he's the autistic now he's just like slow
And he's like, oh, listen to my music.
It's like, yes, by his logic, a three-year-old
playing a xylophone or whatever is my audio is subpar.
Well, whatever.
How about, I didn't change it over, I guess.
Hold on.
Yeah, that's why it's subpar.
Better now, of course, the subpar is on the same microphone.
I mean, it's like someone could have pointed that out before, but you know, is it better now?
You're clicking all I hear is bitching at me all here is a random guy
Harping and like, you know, oh, you know, he's like had a rough day. Let's like
Troll ten times harder than we usually would try him, right?
There you go, right
Then that will be funny because you know
He's already having a bad day. Let's make it worse. This is the mindset of trolls, right?
Hey, look look. Oh, there's a moment of weakness
Like a little like like in Jaws, right? There's oh, there's blood coming out of this like oh, let's all eat the person
Let's all like just wrote like just like a bunch of sharks and go and attack attack
Let's take somebody at their moment of weakness and attack them at that at that point
Who does that? It's like actual enemies not people that are supposed to be like in front. So it's like you're just revealing yourselves people
You're just revealing yourselves. I'm watching the chat tonight. I will watch in the chat very closely
Or 38 people
I know because people were coming in today.
Oh, you don't have anybody in your chat anymore.
Oh, what happened?
What happened?
There used to be 100 people inside here.
Now there's 10 people.
Well, yeah, because I was like leaving the chat,
going back and forth trying to like, you know,
entertain by showing these clips
and then we had technical difficulties.
Yeah, well, thank you, random guy.
I appreciate that.
I do appreciate the donation and that.
But,
Makes me happy is like, you know, there's actually just like a little bit of respect understanding and like, you know
kindness that's a really
But you know, it's gonna be money, too
It does make the medicine go down a little easier, right? So thank you for that
Yep, ten dollar holler random guy you you sponsored the panel for tonight you did it
And can I say you do that?
Okay, random guide. Let me know if you want anything in particular on the
on the banner hold on one sec that
Because I do keep my promises guys and I do
Want to say I do appreciate
Sponsoring panels and that kind of thing
If the patrol is donating, they obviously don't hate me that much, right?
Obviously not, and thus money means just nothing to them.
Okay, so I don't know if you have a channel random guy that you want to promote or somebody else's.
If you want to say, you know, summer's panel or whatever panel you like, let's see, it is 841.
Midnight
12 a.m
Okay
Random guys check out the banner. Tell me if it's okay
And what color you'd like
Okay, I'll just make a nice blue for now
Here we go
Okay
All good
And see the banner guys guys random guy has sponsored the panel for the next three hours
The next three hours random guy could not be gong off the show
Um, and oh that's sure so random guy that I what did I did I ask you for that?
Did I say did I say hey random guy? I'm gonna need that from you. No
So what why are you saying? I'm a grifter. How is that a grifter when you you on your own accord with your own decision?
Your own adult mind donated to me and then now I'm at fault as
A grifter because you donated to me
Unsolicited okay
Hold on. I'm just gonna be confused. I'd explain it to me exactly exactly right right exactly I
Want to explain I want to explain
How it's grifting and you just saw I put a banner up with your your name on it, right?
I even say sponsor the panel. I was like, you know, I'll give him the panel, right?
Who's she hold on what's going on there's other chats going on here
The haters keep your numbers up and are obviously drawn to me.
Well, yeah, that's why I have to monetize the hate.
That's why I'm going to be making, like, you know, basically much immersion dice that's
going to be trolling me because...
That will sell to the haters. I mean, I'm actually a brilliant person, you know
It's like a big nobody else figures out how to monetize the hate. Oh, I'm hated. Let's like, you know, ignore the haters
Let's like ban all the haters blah blah blah blah. Yeah
I mean, it's like certainly I will like time them out and some of them might just like annoying me enough to ban forever
But I think maybe you'll be able to make use of some of them, right?
Everyone wants it once a psyche is turning into a fish choco
Sweatshirt everyone's in Lenore hoodie Lenore hoodies are only like $60. I mean that what a great deal
I mean, but it is Lenore, you know, I'm just kidding. They're $40, but it's still
The relationship is unsustainable, I'll be back broke by September. Oh, sure you will share you will well
It's like, you know what maybe just like, you know
The thing about money is that you can always make more of it
It's just figuring out how sometimes because sometimes, you know, there's some certain avenues will be kind of blocked, right?
Like I can't become a lawyer tomorrow. I can't you know, I can't become Howard Stern tomorrow, you know
I get a half a billion dollar contract
Right. I can't just like become that
so
you know
Yeah, it's the find other ways to the the
Pot of gold
There's always a will there's a way right so anyway
Oh shit, so hopefully piranha does show up because piranha you have a card tonight. You have a bit of card about you
I have Sam and I got you for a card
Who else is getting a card somebody else is gonna get a card? Um, I think Empress Janet will get one
And see there's me some Kings let me see
Hard to figure out the Kings though
If Sandman is going to be a king, I'll put Sandman as a king.
Also, we got pages. We need pages.
But it would be too. I already have pages like the High Priestess, so.
Page can't be a page unless I make a couple pages.
I'm not going to do the JT chariot thing.
Hey, Isaiah, thank you so much.
Okay, Isaiah, you got a panel too, you know, in the future.
You can run it probably, you know, as soon as you'd like to but yeah, thank you. I say I appreciate that. Let me just go
Thank him for that. Thank you guys, you know, I
Do appreciate everything, okay
There we go, I just want to make make sure I thank you and
Let you know I do appreciate you even some of the trolls and some of the trolls don't hate me
Sorry boo boo concentration camp. Look is not cute. Okay, so that kind of person guys anybody that starts talking about oh
You have HIV you look like you're from Auschwitz. I mean
My maybe if that's amusing to you. You need to check your
Kind of sense of humor, I don't find Holocaust jokes funny I don't find
Things about HIV funny, you know, I don't
I don't think they're funny. I don't have HIV. I wasn't in a concentration camp
But I have enough empathy for those that were to like say hey
Like why why use that as a joke and why use that as a funny premise. It's not funny
There's people do some things people laugh at are just confusing to me. You understand guys my right Henry
Sati the alchus in my right or my wrong
You need to ask for PCP for them to send out home health care and physical therapy. Okay. I don't know what they're talking to
You need to be unmodest so you can start blocking again. Okay. You want to go do you want to?
You do I mean, I'll give it back to you if you don't want it, but there you go. You can be a modder. It's fine
Who else I think they're a person. I think that there's someone in panel verse
I'm not sure about Amanda needs to let me know if they're okay, but
Don't disappoint me. Don't disappoint me. Okay, if I give you a moderator don't disappoint me
Oh, so Nancy doesn't see my live up. Do you guys see it? Do you guys see my live it is up?
I'm gonna ban this extra innings person
Guys, let me know if I make a mistake, okay?
Let me know
Mod other the other mods. Can you just watch to make sure I'm not making mistakes?
I'm just like using my intuition. I thought it was pretty good
But um
Am I okay hold on
Okay, they make a mistake guys anybody anybody they make a mistake
Okay
It's okay
Only Greeks are gods. Well, I mean that there is a Greek can't beyond but there's a Roman pantheon. I
Mean, yeah, they're the original the original maybe archetypes
But they are universal
There's a love God. There's a god of women
There's a God of thought. There's usually like some kind of
Artificer God
She got a war
There's a God of justice. There's a God of victory. There's a God of
Well, there's a God for basically everything we'll go look at India. There's a billion of them, right?
Oh, yeah, now I already started the panel.
I say a random guy did a panel, too.
And so it's already open.
I mean, I didn't put the link.
I'm sorry, I'll pin the link.
It is open and then but you yeah, you get a you get a panel the next panel
I say or whenever you call it, you know, you get you get to call a panel
for your donation and I just want to thank you again and am I doing everything right guys?
I'm trying to I bet are you banned? Yes, you banned your friend bulbous juice. Oh,
Oh, and you're trying to juice right juice
There's that okay, here we go
Hi, what's up, man, sorry the screen's dark again about to drive
That answer oh
Just a little stress today, and then you know
It's like you know I get a little bit moody sometimes, and then it's like you know also I get when I get stressed out
I get a little bit crazy.
Okay, so Nancy can't find my live.
Did you even have problems finding a live tonight?
Did you get a notification tonight?
Because maybe, I don't know if I, if I,
The live were.
You're burping, you're burping, hold on.
I'll get it, I'll get it, I'll get it.
Okay, I just need to let Nancy know about my I'll be right back. I'm just a winner. We're gonna reply this one
Switch
I
Okay, I say I say are you there? Oh, we have Trevor here. Hold on Trevor's here. Does it sound better? Yeah, it's
Hey, Trevor
Hey, psych. Hey, Isaiah. How are you guys? Hope everybody's having a good night
It's going on man, doing okay. How are you Isaiah? Good to see you sir. Good to see you psych. Hope you're having a good night
It's getting better. It's gonna a little bit better, but
a little bit stressful.
What are the boys?
What's been going on, fella?
What's been going on, psych?
Well, my bike has been like, you know,
the battery thing was fried, the charger.
My neighbor like went and bought the part
and fixed it and everything.
But then I went and like, it was working.
And then I was like, my bike's fixed.
I was so excited.
I got on the bike and started riding to the store
that I had my lock around like the wheel.
and like it got all tangled with the chain and like now then the chain fell out and like it's all
stuff is coming out of everywhere i don't know it's like i need to have the bikes fixed again
my neighbor will be able to do it he had to do it for a few days or come over for a few days but
it's just like stressful until then because i feel like i fucked it up again when i had it fixed and
like then i went to the store the guy was like my car got declined because i finished like uh
i got you know there's some charge like from this week that like just got posted when i was on the
He almost didn't leave me, like, leaves the store.
He was, like, about to call the police and stuff.
He said he was banned from the store.
He'd let me leave with one harder lemonade and one cigar.
And I had, like, five bucks cash.
And then I came here, and then people were, like, you know,
a little bit mean to me, too, in my chat.
So I get.
But having a bad day.
So you said you left the store with a hard lemonade,
a cigar, and five bucks.
No, not ten bucks. It was like, you know, I had five bucks cash
And so that's what I like left with him with him with so it paid for like the the drink and the cigar like the five bucks
I had and then I had it like leave behind like the two other drinks and the other cigar
And then my it was like, you know, I got charged on my card like
Randomly, so I'm like actually a little bit overdrawn, but that's okay
I mean I'll be good tomorrow, but it's just like stressful at this time and then like you know, no, okay. I'm okay. I'm okay
Okay, people are just like
Aren't you a Michigan I say or am I wrong you're a Michigan Ohio no Ohio he's an Ohio he's an Ohio
oh shit god damn it yeah you know how are you isaiah if you don't mind me asking i'll
sign a cleveland uh who are you really you're about yeah you're like four and a half hours from
me isaiah can i ask you can i always ask any everybody when they say they're close to cleveland
my favorite radio show is out of cleveland i listen to it every morning over it's called yes
I know. Yeah, if anybody from Cleveland says they don't know what that show is, they're liars.
And everybody knows Rover. Everybody
love, hate, whatever. I don't listen to Rover no more because Jeffrey, I'm just tired of all the jokes
on Jeffrey being like the fucking like anchor of the show half the time.
So yeah, yeah, I can understand that either lot. Did you hear that deeter's not there anymore?
I did not know that that's crazy. Yeah, his wife passed away his wife passed away, and he just stopped showing up
His wife died of cancer. Oh
Stop showing up to the show
Damn, that's crazy. Yeah. Yeah. No, I love that show. I love that show
But anyways, I don't want to monotonize the chat. What else you got going on psych?
what's going on buddy well i'm good i'm doing good otherwise like i've been on
tiktok doing like an hour a day on tiktok like doing readings and stuff
i was monetized there actually within three days able to start my own membership and stuff
but um you know the next step of my monetization has been there for a few weeks i need i just
And so then I'll be a next step of monetization and then
Then the next step after that is like 30,000 followers or something like that
But I'll be able to get there eventually too
You know and I do like you know on YouTube I get like maybe like 10 15 likes and I get some dislikes every episode on
Tiktok date a like is just you know
If you one person can give as many likes as they want it's just you have to double tap the screen as many times
And that's a like so on a tiktok I get like
8,000 10,000 likes and so it's like I'm like wow like you know people are like sitting there tapping the screen
10,000 times what I'm on on tiktok, and they can't even like on YouTube most people can't even say you know just one time
It's my best fucking friend. I love fucking psyches. My best fucking friend close the door
Sorry about that. Yeah, you do a big dog
Sorry, 50 live viewers and 10 likes.
Beg it easy, guys.
Beg it easy, man.
Are you behaving like Joe?
Bagels is up in here, oh, shit.
Oh, I'm behaving, baby.
But I might be smelling a little bit.
Fair enough, fair enough.
What are you up to, Joe?
It's good to see you.
It's good to see you, Joe.
Oh, you know, just drinking and stinking.
Just drinking and stinking, big dog.
Fair enough.
I mean, you could probably smell me from 10 miles away, Psyche.
Why'd your elbow smell like you know a fence?
Your elbow looks pointy as shit right now.
What the hell was that?
It's not my elbow.
It's my shoulder.
See, it's my shoulder.
It's what I call my shoulder blade.
You're shoulder.
I'm sorry, not your elbow.
Your shoulder looks like your elbow.
It's what I'm talking about.
Yeah, they're actually...
You know how it's called shoulder blade?
Mine is actually like a blade.
It's actually...
I just have knives.
Damn.
Don't let that thing touch me.
You know what? I'm going to hit a thumbs up right now.
I'm going to hit a thumbs up right now because I'm going to hit a thumbs up.
I'm trying to like you
How are you sir? Thank you. Oh, I'm good sir fucking just live in the northeast Ohio dream
It's a landscaper, you know, like every other male here. Oh
Just like the show just like the show very nice
Rovers morning glory reference
What up, Trevor?
What up, guys?
CLI.
Yeah, Cleveland loves you.
They will never slay that on the show.
I don't know why.
Are they?
Cleveland Rocks. Member Drew Carey said Cleveland Rocks.
That's what I remember.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Good ol' Drew Carey show.
I don't like to think of those fond-ass memories before TV and media went to shit. Makes me sad.
I know, I did.
They drew a carry a shoe, just lying and sitting out of the way.
Good.
Oh, no, you're good.
Well, one of my favorite TV shows, Home Improvement,
I actually found on this free app called Swing.
No, I'll be in that series.
I found it on a free app called Swing and I watched it.
I'm not fucking paying money to watch a fucking TV show.
Oh, dude.
Let's be real too like and that's like they're 30 20 30 40-year-old TV shows
Like why do we have to pay to watch that shit that's been re-streamed a thousand fucking times?
Exactly! You already made your money off the show! God you fucking money hungry pieces of shit, Tim Allen!
Just play home and prove it for me!
Well, Jerry Seinfeld's a billionaire
Dude
Sign called show to streaming he's a billionaire
Always be full house and Bob Stagg is a fucking billionaire
He's a love. He's a love my name is
They just sold they're on HBO right now, but they just apparently they own the right stall. There's stuff and they sold it to paramount plus and
for like hundreds of
Me right now Trevor the next can you are the next few years they do
You fucking bag imagine it being you made a cartoon
and we just sold it for 700 million dollars like Trevor remember that cartoon we made in high school
we just sold it at Paramount for 800 million dollars I'm Trevor Parker or Tre Parker I was
getting a fucking blowjob right now from a fucking Spanish block they're too Jewish for that they
The Canadian in a moped up to it, they'd say sorry all the time.
Talk to the woman in a carbon's voice, like,
Hey, me, Carmen, like, oh, shit, creepy fuck.
All right, since South Park was drawn off, though,
did you guys see the most recent episode?
I guess the second episode of the season
got released, didn't see that.
The first episode of the season?
Dude, old school, funny fucking South Park.
That's how I describe it. It's fucking good ass South Park comedy. Was it good?
Yeah, it was phenomenal. It was fucking
Joe you shut up you lovable fucking idiot
Joe is such an idiot, but for some reason I find him endearing. He's such a fucking idiot, but there's something
There's something about them. I'm not sure what it is
It does matter.
Wish you psyche.
But either way, yeah, no, I watched this watch the first episode of this newest season of South Park
I stopped I haven't watched it in like at least five six seasons
But my buddy showed it to me the other day. Oh, it's fucking
Watch you shut the fuck up. I'd love to watch
Understand you bitch
You cute lovable bitch you're breaking up
you're breaking up you're breaking up baby boy
oh hey joe baby bitch joe do you need your ass spanked probably be on the video joe do you need
your ass spanked do you need your ass spanked i haven't watched self-marking so long but i will
check it out isaac i will check it out it's totally it is worth the f***ing watch
I haven't said that a bunch about my shit.
Somebody in the chat said HIV panel only me only me. I don't think guys they have or Joe have HIV probably me though
probably me
Your spirit is probably a faggot on and off like he don't you have the guts to come up and say like faggot panel
Like on his main channel, so we switched to an all just the cusses out. Good job spirit. You fucking loser
Hey guys, hey Joe Joe you're fucking idiot, but for some reason I love you you're endearing
Thank Isaiah. It was nice to talk to you. I'm gonna get going. I'll talk to you guys later. Bye
Sorry to run you off the panel, but that now I just got to sit here and talk to a grizzly bear drinking beer like I'm not I'm not in the mood for this.
Nigger nigger nigger nigger nigger nigger nigger. I'm sorry psych, but you left me up here alone
So I had to have a little fun by myself
I'm actually jerking off right now. I'm actually naked. I'm whacking off the psych's last stream
It's like do me a favor bend over real quick. I'm almost finished
Where'd everyone go? I'm so sorry
Okay, guys. Well, I was downloading some more of these uh of these shorts
I don't know if you guys want to see but I think you guys will like them. Hold on
choose files
Hopefully I can put these up with a big problem. Okay, resense
Save from Chrome.
Okay, so here's one called the Discord Shocker.
622 PAM, okay, that's not right, okay.
Okay, 904 PAM, okay, so this one health scenario.
Health, something.
I do apologize guys, we're gonna be right up and running.
As soon as I can
RIP server, okay, or should I okay?
I know 3 p.m. I said p.m. Okay, I think we're doing okay guys
How are we doing whoo, but I'm sorry everybody you know everybody like ended up leaving after that one
Okay, so I got it. Did it work? Let me check. Oh, it didn't work. Okay. I add file
Drive. My Drive. Save from Chrome. Okay. So, let's see. We have this health scenarios.
Exploring limitations. Hope that's good. Okay, confirm. Okay, it's working. It's working.
Yeah, so these are these are really funny. It's when uh, it's when uh,
this guy, oh
My god, oh, hold on. You know, it's fine. It's fine. I
Think you'll like this. Oh
It's just a it's kind of a disaster tonight guys. It's one of those nights. Okay. We'll drive. Please please just work
Please it's like the way being guys the way the audience is waiting. Everyone's gonna kiss talk. Come on
It's always like everything happens at once
Okay, I think it's coming up.
I said I think you guys will think it's funny.
Well, I'm gonna rock the screen.
of its stress.
Would she like be bedridden after she was that you she would just be laying in bed
It's gonna be a thing. It's gonna be like she's just like oh god. Let me get off of you
I'm suffocating you, but you know I die under her ass
Well does anybody in chat guys do you relate to this anybody have that?
You ever like that one you're another one
We'll take up that one
feet, okay
And we got more coming you guys are gonna infer treat you like that that one
One minute. Okay. You have one minute. Okay. I'll be mad at me
What happened to that dude? I haven't seen him since remember when he was like had a health scare everyone was like
Oh, he needs to go to the hospital. I don't know what happened to him after that
Okay, sorry if I'm sideways
I'm trying to play these these clips because these are funny as fuck. So this is another one coming up
Everyone's saying
And as it was born the doctor slept his mama. Hey, Ash
You can't wait to see what happens. Yeah, can I basically? I know I'm getting offended by these two, but it's in a good way
Hmm
Take you a little bit. Oh, it's ready. It's ready. Here we go
Who the fuck do you think you are you're trying to like talk to me like what I
Can't be with a skinny bitch. I'm
Fill with a fucking model like growing up. I don't give a fuck about
Size zero I
Enjoy fat bitches
I didn't say I didn't say you I just said it was I thought the story was shot
Like you put it a very very very like you think that I can't get with fucking like I never said any
I consider good-looking bitches. It's like shut the fuck up. You're a nobody like
You can look at me, you can see, I look way better than any of you motherfuckers.
Well, I don't think it's not really good.
You're just starting to compare to me.
Uh, just because I like a fucking...
Well, no one said there's anything wrong.
Hey!
What?
I could take your bitch.
Like, any fucking bitch that any of these losers that have, I've taken them.
I don't walk them.
I love that bitches. It's not so hard to understand. You're so fucking stupid. You can't understand that a
God likes
fat bitch
Fucking retard lady. You're a weirdo. Yeah, pedophile
Wow, okay, that was pretty crazy, okay, let's see what else okay, I'm gonna save this one
Okay
Let's make sure there's it if there's any other ones I
Know it's pretty it is pretty shocking right? It's the language, right?
but
We will continue
Yeah, I know he was terrible he was terrible right a cameo side, but it's okay. It's okay a camera camera, right?
Oh, okay. Got it
No waiting I know I know it's a little bit long, but he's got you get straight to the crash. Yeah, I know
I was kicked out of the old guys the only the only closer liquor store is 7-eleven which is like a mile away, and I don't have a bike
You may have to get the distress is put on me you guys
I'm not even yeah one time I asked for some fish taco money, and I never will hear the end of it
So I'm not asked if I need to like you know get a bottle of orange juice
You know on credit
So I can drink the tequila that they'll be fine. Okay, so hold on a second
I have one more for you guys one more just one more it's gonna be one more hold on
hi hi hi baby i'm a beautiful baby
bear with me guys
hi baby oh i love you i love you i love you oh baby babe
I have one more for the chat I have one more for the chatty chat the chatty chat chat one more
Let me see not that this okay that not doubt not that okay this is it right here
Okay
Okay confirm
Well, you're kissing me. You're kissing you're like you like to kiss me kisses big
I love you, baby. I love you mine is a nori my Lenore no nor
My little kitty cat. You're my little kitty. You're the best cat
So much I love you so much
Okay
It's coming up guys working the last one and I'm sorry
One last one guys
Can I kiss can I kiss
I love you my kitty cat you're my kitty cat you like to
She's so sweet. Oh, you're my sweetheart. You're my sweetheart. I love you
Here you go guys last one, okay
Toke over the water fuck holy shit, there's no water. Oh my god
Oh no, you're gonna die one day. Sorry. I didn't mean to die on your screen.
You'll help my ratings.
Good. I mean, I'm sorry I'm died. I didn't die.
Okay.
I mean, I thought it was kind of funny. I'm sorry I died on your stream.
And I was like, maybe I'll help the ratings. I don't know.
I'm an evil, evil person. I'm an evil person. Okay.
What do I think like that? Why do I think that? Why do I say that Lenore? I was mean what I say that I don't care about ratings
I don't care
I love you so much
Yeah, I was kid going to JC's panel. It's always getting your shit face. Yeah, he was oh, yeah, I do have the link pin guys come on up
Yeah, they told me that you are going to touch back to your fingertips years ago, and yeah, you guys like that
I think they're pretty funny. Hey, babe
Hey, look, hi
Don't see them for a while, huh? Hi
Hi guys that was from one
And those are like an hour long stream because that would let me do like a short stream
I kept trying to like do like a longer one. It was like there's too many clips
So I did though an hour shoo
It found 30 clips that it found worthy of clipping on that one hour show imagine my 11 hour show
So I'm gonna have to start getting a subscription to this and like doing these shorts and like having also some episodes indicate
Oh, you love it. What more trash could be in here?
Well rain first of all let me first of all we can look at your boyfriend your boyfriend who is rude to like a really nice woman last night
Said really really bad things to her
Let's see and I actually was nice enough to make a tarot card of him at his request. So there's your boyfriend rain
Okay, that's your boyfriend and
But you know what? If you want to be so negative about the people in my chat, even if they're trolls, they're my trolls. They're not your trolls.
You don't talk about my trolls in a disparaging way, okay? So you can just take a little timeout, okay?
Erase your reign. I'm going to erase you for a little bit. Put you on timeout.
So there.
But that's your boyfriend right there. And you see, I don't know if you're that cat or something like that, but...
Yeah, see he's writing around with some other pussy. I
Said Wolfman doll and it put a maybe like a cat and a cape or something like that, but
Interesting
Yeah, the North inside
But I'm not gonna use that card to share it, but it is it is her boyfriend
Yeah, I mean she shouldn't stay that shit. Oh, oh look at all these losers in this chat
Yeah, okay. Well. Yeah, just call everyone a loser and you're in the chat by the way
You're in the chat, right? We're everyone else is a loser. Oh, look at all the trash in this chat
and please
If it's if it's trash, it's my trash, okay, I like it. I like them
Anybody who's here is like is here because I want them here
What's up, bro? Hi
My buddy, uh
He hunts for shit with a metal detector. He found us over the years
Mmm, and I might go cash it in for him. You want to see something creepy?
Look at this
Can I have that good God, that's terrifying. You want to see the dude looks like Satan, bro
Look, let me look at these closer. It's a devil, bro
I'll show them again. He's like, I'm gonna get to this fucking scary. Not too bad. They're cute. It's fucking creepy, dude
And is this a motherfucking? What is this thing? Is that is a ruby?
Is that worth money, dude? Well, I mean, if it's a real ruby, but it went to this thing
It went to this day's work. It's fucking 14k bro. You know your rich people like to have a lot of fake stuff though
That's the thing. It's like 14 karat gold. This thing's a fucking nugget
that's a nugget bro my nugget well you got very you know you get your friends
very lucky you know what you know it's really interesting that i was just
looking at shit there's a what there's a website called um called
I forgot what it's called, but it's like it has like it's like you sell there
You know you buy and sell and they have a state sales
And so I was like I went to the straight to the estate sales because I know the best deals are there
It's some cool stuff. Hey babe one
It's some pretty cool stuff. That's all the most of that shit's gold. I just I just checked everything with a loot
Well, congratulations. I hope that the output all is you know gold and I hope you know you and your friend cash in
You know, I you deserve it. Oh, yeah
Well, congratulations. I'm really happy for you
Lockets are always clout. You're cool. Okay. Yeah, it could be a serial killer souvenirs
Yeah, well a lot of like the I like the police options too because a lot of the police auctions are like, you know
Basically drug lords that are you know prison for the rest of their life and then they sell everything in the mansion
They the temporary mansion they had and it all goes back to the people, right? So
But good night, Sponky. Have a good night. Okay, hopefully
Are you talking up? There you go
Who a little bit
We're cranky today, but I think everything will work. Everything will work out, you know
By is your e-bike is it because your e-bike dude? Yeah
I'm kind of pissed off because it was my because it's me just me being stupid
It's like but I think it's like sometimes I get so stressed out and it's a women's but things finally get fixed
And then I screw her up again. Like I was stressed dude. I was stressed because it's
You should be glad you made it that long on life like oh, I know I am I seriously
Everyday I know died at like 30 dude like you know gay people have a lifespan of 30 years old
So that's like the average gay person's lifespan is 30 years old
Yeah, it's like a very short and so I've already lived way longer than the average gay person
So now you're miserable pretty much well there's nothing sadder than an old queen and I'm getting into that territory, you know
Um, or it's like, yeah, I'll be like the, I'll be like that, you know, that eccentric old man
Without, you know, anybody
Loves him, right?
What are you gonna do then? Oh, yeah, I think you're already there
Oh, yeah
Where you go from here? No, it's been it's been over for ten years
I'm saying every every moment I've lived since then is basically just a bonus and so I mean I've already already
Had my life expectancy so everything here is just a bonus the bonus rounds for me for like the last 15 years
That's okay, I bet you
Go ahead and date now. I'm like, I'm I would give it up on love. I really have like, I mean
I don't give up on love. I believe in love for other people. I don't believe in love for me
But other people sure
They do think it's possible
but
I'm just done like I'm on borrowed time basically
Bring rain back. No
No, Jamie
Because Jamie I banned her for 30 minutes like what?
It's gonna be that it's gonna be an issue 30 minutes because she said that there's garbage in the chat
I'm allowed to say there's garbage in the chat, but I don't I wouldn't even say that because I believe in people
And so someone that's gonna like oh, there's just a bunch of garbage in your chat
I don't think that's a very positive way to start the conversation
I don't know I
Don't deserve love. Okay. Thanks. Gooma. Yeah, I kind of believe the same thing. I don't deserve
Just say pass me by right
It's not Ruby worth money, dude
Probably especially if it's a star Ruby
Where do I bring it pawn shop yeah, right or
No, I probably the best I wouldn't take nothing to a pawn shop, dude. They rip you off
Yeah, but you can buy it back though. I mean, that's the thing. It's like it's like put there for a temporary
amount of time so you're like I need money like from a
No, you can like, you know, you can like just constantly be be pawning it and you can make like a lot of money from it
Just putting it, you know month at a time or something like that
You'll basically make your money back pretty quickly. I don't think that's how these things work, man
Don't know they can tell you if it's real. Yeah, they certainly will. Yeah, you know praise it
They'll put those definitely praise of free a jeweler. Okay. Yeah
Watch I will praise it too. They'll probably
Heal a little bit less, but then it's like if there's any if there's anything that ever goes awry with like a serial number or anything
You know they can I
Don't know. Oh
Yeah, I know she can't get like a lot of people can't you like this is the nicest like the coolest nicest lady on last night and her name is like D oceans and she's just like her experiences her stories like her sense of humor her like she's just like a great person a beautiful person people coming on say oh you know you're calling her some oh you're some fat so I mean just like
Ridiculous, right? I
Think I want to get this on my front tooth like if it's real
This is a big for your front, too, I mean it's huge dude's massive
Are you with the whole thing in a lot? Yeah, I want to be my whole tooth. Yeah, okay
Well that's the look nowadays, I suppose right the bling
She was sweet. She's a sweet lady and it's like she didn't deserve it, right?
And you know who do you know who do you talk badger?
LD
JT Gotti
Canada Drive ray one that's like five people. I can remember off the top of my head
I was like, hey, I'll bring him on and they all are proceeding today. Oh bring me back up bring back up
I brought them back up and they kept repeating horrible things
Like they can't get the hint. I mean it's like
Or they do and then they're like just going against it. I mean, it's like
But why because that you know
That's like hey, I'm gonna be my friend here my really cool friend
Like I love this person, you know we're friends for a long time and it's like. Oh, yeah
We'll just like, you know, she's this person like trash and like you just make them think that it's like, you know
You're just a loser who has no control their show
Then they'll like you know, and then they'll leave and you know another friend like another good friend
We've ruined you've ruined the relationship again. Yeah, that's all this awesome people want, right?
Why are there reasons to be rude to somebody?
Yes
You can be a new Joe. Yeah, just go ahead and send the $25 and yes
I'll do that hour hour long. You can you can be nude and I'll be I'll be in the speedo
Her people hurt people sometimes, but it's like, you know hurt people also can help people. No Joe
Free you can do it for free you talking about Joe Shirley Shippley. Yeah
What it would happen, I didn't do nothing he's fine. It's fine. Okay. Well, why'd you say do you know what he did?
And then I don't know what did he do? He didn't do anything as far as I know you're right. You're the one that's you're the one
That said what I didn't do shit
Okay, you know you said guess what Joe did I heard you let her run let her run buddy
That's what you said. You said oh, I forgot it what I said. Yeah. Yeah, you said it like just a few seconds ago
Actually, I can I forget why I said it. I mean those wide wide. Why would you but why would you say that like?
Why would you I don't I'm just dude. I'm over here looking at treasure. Okay?
Don't I mean I shouldn't like but good good patience to your treasure and just like you know
Come on the show when you're ready to like you know talk with a normal person and not be so enraptured by shiny things
They will not carry you beyond this world. Certainly. They'll be sorted out by your relatives
When you die
And put it into a garage sale basically, you know, that's how much you know, that's what people do and she will die
You know, yeah, they just they sell they sell their stuff. You sound jealous of my jewelry right now to be honest
I'm so super. I'm so super jealous. I sound like a dude
I don't know. I'm really jealous. I'm so sounds like I am. Oh, that's all I'm thinking about is like
Oh, how much is that worth? They you know the ruby probably three grand three grand plus. Oh, wow
I might as well as oh, it's off myself now. You know, it's like right right. Yeah. Yeah, you should kill yourself
Yeah, cuz you're jealous of my gold real smart. Yeah. Yeah real smart
How about I just ban you for like saying that K yourself what you're not supposed to do and I'm supposed to encourage that on YouTube
I don't know is that you just don't get it, right? I'm guy and so I don't care if you sponsor the panel or not
You're done for the night
Say K yourself, you know, yeah, I don't know like people to get your gear supposed to say go go K yourself
What do you guys think about that?
You should people should that should be allowed on YouTube go go and you're live yourself. That's that's what they believe
Because that's the first thing Q said to me that and other people have said that to me too. Just go unalive yourself
That's something to say to a human being right?
Am I thinking about that booty? Let me see. Yeah, it sounds like bad advice to me, too
No, no, no, he just did I mean he just did random gay guy random gay guy said that
Yeah, he also called me Joe Shirley and that's when I had to join like nobody's gonna call me a woman's name and get away with it
That's a little too far guys
When you start calling men women's names now, you're just sad now. You're just going nuts. Now. You're just going nuts guys
Go up. Oh look what Kim drove here psyche. Can you see this?
See this scooter
Yes, sir. No, do you see that?
What is what happened a scooter? Okay her scooter. That's what Kim drove here. That's what Kim
She's outside talking to her cousin. That's in jail when her cousin
I don't mean to talk shit about her and I am but her cousin was like if you wouldn't accept this call from the fucking penitentiary
And I was like don't accept that call that guy's a fucking murderer and she's like, oh, that's my cousin
That's my cousin. I'm like, I don't give a fuck if your cousin's a killer
Let's not let's not I know I'm being silly psyche, but I was like Kim they're being that honest with you
I was like Kim take your fucking phone call with your fucking felon cousin your murderer cousin outside
I want to talk to my friend psyche. I want to talk to my friend. Okay?
Well, that's really nice of you. I appreciate that
You damn right it's nice to me. You damn right it is
Thank you
No, you're welcome
mean how many fingers do you need on your phone to hold it like you need two
hands to hold that motherfucker I know some you can use your hands on I got
some you can fucking hold with two heads one hand one hand it's my fucking
firehose oh come on that's gay firehose what is that
man made me say that. Actually,
Sam and made me say that.
Oh, thank you Jamie.
She's outside on the phone with her.
You know her murderer cousin,
but I'll tell her you said that
when she comes back in.
He can be a killer if he wants.
Well, he wants to be and he did.
Ash, he's is that's why he's in jail.
He wanted to be a killer.
Hey, you know what?
When I grew up,
I just wanted to drink and smoke weed,
enjoy my friends panels and have fun.
But if you grow up wanting to be a killer, you can do that too and you'll just live the rest of your life in jail when he fucking corn every day for fucking dinner.
No more steak, no more Burger King, no more fucking Chick-fil-A, you're in jail.
I've been in like county jail.
They never serve corn, I don't think, but I think they did serve like...
really nasty burritos they serve like the little god of jail burrito can you imagine what's in a jail
oh no no everyone was like saying everyone was like everyone was telling me everyone was telling me
oh well you're gonna love the burritos there like they're like oh there's this prison burritos
are they jailed burritos are you going to jail
No, no, not at all. I'm saying I've been
You'll love it like you'll love it like are you they sound like you're getting arrested because they they loved it
They thought it was no because I was going to jail
I went to jail for like three days and they're like you're gonna love it
But let me tell you one thing people like clumsy or gay because who pranks about going to jail again when I was locked up
I did this I did that like who cares like
Yeah, no, no, no, that's but that's like street credit for like people like clumsy. That's like, oh
No, no, no, no every everyone else understand that we understand that we understand that when like I want to go to jail so I can take a shower
Like, you know, it's like, I want to go take a shower with other guys that I'm honest about, he wants to do it.
He wants to do it. Yeah. Yeah.
So I'll pick it up for you.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
He's like, you know, put a broom, put a broom inside of me, put it right now.
He's like, he wanted the broom.
I mean, he was like, the broom was his fantasy.
That's what I mean.
Grab that bar of soap with my ass cheeks and give it back to you.
Like, yeah, I know Jill's gay, but like you're being super gay.
That's what they call clumsy in jail, like gayer than gay.
That was triple G.
Yeah, yeah, yes triple G
right
Now what you like I do fuck you like you're a gentleman you never been to jail you're at least a gentleman
I have been to yeah, I just said I went to jail for like like three days
No, I had a CC who holds their phone with two hands a sissy does look at your little sissy hands holding your phone a little sissy boy
Now I'm fucked with you. It's like that's where it. I was fucking with you
Are you really Joe you're really you're not you're not you're just kidding about getting the reading you're not really
There's outside on the phone. I finally got ten minutes to fucking have a little fun
For she comes in and hits me again. I'm getting abused
Somebody call the police
Well, I got her purse. Hold on. You know what hold on boys
Take a look at this
What is this? Oh?
It's Kim. He's purse. Let's take a little peak
I'm taking a peek, punk this shit. I'm taking a fucking peek. Hold on.
Ooh!
A pack of cookies from my own cabinets.
Wow, these were mine one second ago. Now they're in Kim's purse.
Didn't know that until just now.
Did not know that until just now. Thank you.
Anything else you're very welcome. Oh my god. This is the order on this a fucking dodo, bro
What is this did she get this from crack adona? Why is there a sling shot?
I swear to God I didn't plant these items. Why is there a sling shot in Kim Spurs?
That right there tells me she's been flirt with crack adona that right there gives it all away gives it away
No, I'm sorry. I'm just being silly and I'm drunk, but I am going to her fucking shit fucker. Who's cracker gonna?
Ragadona make slingshots. Oh, she does. Okay. Oh, she's oh, she's that famous. Oh, there's nothing else. Just cookies and slingshots
There was nothing else in there, but cookies and slingshots. Sorry
Like oh, there's gonna be fucking like 70 condoms in there like for Magnum's for like black guys
No, just cookies and slingshots man. Sorry. Sorry about this
Actually psyche, I like you but please take that wig off. That's a fucking wig take that fucking wig off right now
That hair is looking too perfect to be real that is obviously a fucking a fake wig
Fake wave, huh?
No man has that perfect of hair. No man on this earth. It's not perfect. Is that a perfect hair?
Mr. Rude mr. Rudy boy mr. Rude compliment. I'm trying to give you a compliment. Also. Oh
Compliment there's a compliment. Okay. Well, I said no
I'm wearing a wig. I'm wearing a wig. That's a compliment
On earth has your perfect hair also said no man on earth has your hair
But look you look like John Stamos. Why are you trying to look you be an uncle Jesse for Halloween?
Well, you're Halloween costume. Oh, you're not Joe. You're not Jesse. Gonzapales
Kassopoulos
Every word you said would make me smile
He's saying that to Michelle didn't he say that to Michelle is that look kind of strange
No, I'm not bullshitting you even Rick Springfield will kind of be jealous of that fucking hair
I'm a little jealous of it like I wish I could take my hat off me like guys look at this fucking wave of fur
You can say you can show it all from front of me in front of your friends man. I'm doing that on purpose
But joe, you're gonna buy you're gonna buy a little
Joe
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I just want to verify you're gonna buy the reading or you're just bullshitting me making fun of me by saying you're gonna buy
Oh, I'm gonna buy the reading. I'm gonna buy the reading. Okay. That's one of my bones
And it's a half an hour
No, at least an hour. I'll do at least an hour because you guys are like friends
And I'm I mean silly
because I'm just, but if I really wanted to be nude,
I can be nude the whole time you do the reading.
Yeah, no, I actually expect it now
because you said it and I'm looking forward to it.
Now I got you site. I got you man 25. I'll give you 50. I'll give you a tip
I'll tell you I'll buy it for 25 now. I'll give you 25
I'll give you both. I'll give you both like an hour
I'll give you a different tip. All right. I'll give you two tips. All right. Take it where you can get it, buddy
Can I have an actually your neck looks like a stack of dimes that I could snap my fingers and fuck. Oh, sorry about this
I'm just saying man. You got nice hair
But your head is on like a fucking stick like that neck do a little do a couple of these every day like put like do this
No, so that neck up my coins. Yes. I don't know. I your neck and hold up a sexy head like that
How can your neck hold up that sexy fucking head? It's called it's called magic
Did you believe we are magic?
Do anybody in the chat it's actually pronounced tear rot
No, it's not. It's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it
No, you know what, listen, I'm up here to have fun, but right there, that is disrespectful.
Because I actually can ride the rides at Six Flags.
When BG goes to Hershey Park, they're like, sir, you're a cool guy, like we know you're
from YouTube, but you're just not tall enough.
You just can't do it.
And then BG goes back to his car and puts phone books in his shoes, and we're like, sir, we
know who you are.
You just put platform shoes on.
and then they're like, then they kicked him out of the park.
All right, go it's like, they talked about me first.
I don't have anything else to say.
I mean, just a shock, right?
Well, man, you're being called the male BG like oh, you're the
I think the worst thing to be called the worst thing. I mean a person
Well, actually, there's a second worst thing the worst thing could be like oh, you're like clumsy then that oh no
That's the absolute worst, you know, if you have your camera, I'll leave mine on
Not only do you get that you get the you get the business end of the broom
But you also
Will save up your eyebrows and just go with the afterward, right? You're gonna be like, oh, yeah
But I'll tell you one thing right now. It's like
If I ever did have a broom on my asshole, I would never like tell it to this panel or like this people because you know how this chat is and clumsy so retarded.
He don't even drink beer. He was just like feeling emotional one night. He's like, yeah, I got a broom shoved up my ass in jail. Like why would you say that?
Even if it happened, why the fuck would you say that you dumb fucking retard? I don't even care.
I don't care about him or the broom. I'm just saying he seems like an idiot to say that. Oh, I know
No, no, you keep that there's a couple things you keep to yourself and one will be a broom going on my asshole
That's one thing I might have to
Maybe maybe
Thank you. No, thank you for letting me on soggy
Make one more cigarette through this and I'll call tonight. I know I've run. I know I wear my welcome out sometimes
I can't be an asshole
Yeah, it's not like it's the worldwide webs. Yeah clumsy, but never we're never hear that again
Yeah, you say something gay. We'll never hear that again
That ass is as clumsy
Yeah, what I'm about to
long can Kim talk to her
like don't they have a ti
it's fucking, it's the e
lying to me because it's
They don't let prisoners
at one in the fucking mor
like a lot. I don't even
but let's go through her
No, but let's lie when she comes in and act like we did when she comes in psyche
Listen when she comes in do me a favor be like ha ha ha ha ha we saw it's in your first game like laugh at her
Hey, is that fair? Thank you
Be like well you got cookies condoms and fucking carrots like the triple C
No, there was what was in there?
Let's go do it again. Let's look at it again guys. Oh what?
I was not in your purse
Prove it
Prove I was in your purse
Kim, Kim, Kim, Kim, he was in it
He was in it, he was in it
They were mine
No, they were mine
Why are my cookies in their purse?
Kim, we saw everything in the purse
We saw it
They're my cookies
It's like this is personal
We saw everything
Kim, Kim, he's a
Kim
Did you see when you when you kiss Joe on the camera and do you remember when I kissed Joe?
Oh my god, not the cheese the cheap brand that's a cheap brand
You're still on the phone
Oh and actually psyche made a good point. How are you talking to somebody in jail at one in the morning?
They don't let people make you do
Oh, I apologize. I thought you were saying it
Well, then I didn't say I didn't say I am he's lying saying you're gonna call me a fucking dummy
I didn't say anything. Give me that phone. He wants to call me his house. Um, I'd like to talk to this man
Yeah, can you call me back? Yeah, can you?
All right, I'll call you back. Let's have a fuck up, boy. Yo, you keep talking. I'll just let him bust your ass
Stop talking shit. Well, you don't know. I'm on the phone with really stop talking shit. That's not a good idea
Well, you're the one threatening me.
Sorry about this, Psyche.
No, it's not.
See how it is, see how it is.
That is
Twice to take it outside because I'm being a gentleman. I'm on my friend's panel
I'm literally getting ready to get my friend's panel
So you could take it outside
You're lie high in yeah, you're lying
But that's okay to
I love you, man. Sorry
Kim, you're fine. I'm an asshole, Kim.
Get the hell out of my house.
He's an asshole. He's an asshole.
He actually didn't get a serious cousin.
He didn't get a serious cousin.
Well, who are you?
It's like, listen, I'll give you $20, Kim.
Who sang you're an asshole?
Didn't say what actor sang that song, male actor?
What actor sang that song tonight?
Dennis Leary, you piece of shit.
You didn't even get by.
You would have never guessed it.
Come on, you would have never guessed it.
And you won't know what right I don't mean is the worst biggest asshole
Maybe you shouldn't be singing this song
Laughing and screaming and carrying on
Maybe they're right wouldn't they tell me I'm wrong
Nah
Look look it's like oh look it's like you right now
go ahead fix it baby go ahead don't need to come on he looks gay right shake it shake it
No, the reason I told her to look at you was like look at this hairy animal Kim
To me give me my pen may I pick your pen up may I pick your pen up? Yes, I bet
Give me my hand by the way. Well, give me my pen. Oh, and then you snatch it
Apologize
I did show them your slingshot. I ain't gonna lie. I showed them. We found your cookies and slingshots
No, we didn't find your what there's a knife in there. Yeah. All right. I better stop
Looks hairless almost just look it is sweet. Oh, don't shake it around site. Geez. You ain't got to shake it all around
What up grim reaver
You remember I don't want to know. Yeah, I don't you know, right? You're right. Ash. I wish I didn't even look
I wish I didn't look at that purse
The only thing I want to say is like the day before a good times birthday
Ozzy Osbourne died and the day after a good times birthday Hulk Hogan died
So I can't wait till next year to see what who's what celebrities good times birthday kills next year
Do you want to have this respect what your president was?
Oh, it's talking about Donald Trump.
Stop it. Shut up.
Come on.
Arm wrestling.
Yeah.
Did anybody see the cloud?
Somebody in chat go to Google and type in Hulk Hogan's cloud.
There was a fucking cloud that day over his funeral site.
Remember when Hulk Hogan used to pose and make a muscle
and stick his arm out like this?
Yeah
There was a fucking cloud right over Hulk Hogan's funeral that looked like that so I do believe
You're making things up now Joe, it's fine
nobody heard about that cloud but don't look it up on your phone Kim so I can show them on your phone tape in
Hulk there wasn't a cloud a cloud in a cast like Hulk there was no cloud on a whole crew
that
No one life and my life my childhood. I fucking was a hulk a maniac. I know you
Did hit me in the heart strings like
Everybody
Give me that cloud. You're not gonna type in Hulk Hogan's cloud cam for real. You're not gonna fucking man
All the fun all the fucking things I do for you. You're not gonna take that
Oh, how else to take the type in Hulk Hogan, maybe because my phone is
Joe she's literally holding her phone typing
Sorry about this guys and you literally
Can I show it to my friend psyche please
Just click the images there right there. There you go. Well, it's like you hold on one second, buddy
How does it look just like Hulk Hogan making the post and that's real that was right
No, it's not. It's fake. It's a fake. It's a fake thing to make
Hogan, Hogan, like his Zeus or something. Right. He's Zeus.
He's Zeus. He's a store. He's a store. So, Hulk Hogan is
store now, right?
Smoking up for Hulk Hogan's ashes like he's smoking up for the
Hulkamaniacs. That's why I fuck with psyche. He don't play
around. He gets high. That's high as this guy. Oh, look at
that cloud. Damn.
I love you. I love you guys.
I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I
love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love
I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love
you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you.
I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you.
That's a break, but Hulk Hogan wasn't wearing pants. So that's actually an accurate
So it was like it was more like you was a more like Joe on the weekends. You go to the gate
Kim right now, I will tell you what he had
What did he have he was in the movie
Princess Pride, but Hulk Hogan was in Thunder and Paradise, but Hulk Hogan was a movie star.
It was nothing compared to the Princess Bride. The Princess Bride is a cult classic.
Did you bring me a beer? The Princess Bride is a cult classic.
What did you bring after? Were you on that phone?
No, I didn't bring you a picture.
You know what I want. You know what I want.
I'll go grab my home beer. You know what? No, I'll grab it. I'll grab my home beer. Okay. Okay, and I want my fucking slingshot back
You want to bet?
What's your favorite thing about psyche Kim? Like when you when we come up on his panel
What's your favorite thing eats the pig in the shit or something? He's not even here
But what's your favorite thing about him?
He's cool people as you shove a cookie down my cookies down your cookie down your gullet
All right, well, you know got a cough on them
You did you were such a liar
You are such a fucking liar.
I'm a fucking boy, they're mine.
I literally bought them from the bar.
They sell cookies at the bar.
Yeah, exactly.
That's fucking disgusting.
Bar cookies, bar cookies, how about a bar?
I mean, I could understand they sold peanuts
or like a fucking like chicken nuggets.
Like you drank 10 beers, were you like a fucking cookie?
Like no, I'm not fucking retarded.
Actually, yeah.
Exactly smash. I said no, it was barred 100% right. No one's barred was a great Hulk Hogan movie
No, don't they just say oh my god. Hulk Hogan is one of our favorites. Don't
Move Lee by the way move Lee move Lee where
Rushler
Work predominantly in the movie and it wasn't about rumble all the way or rumble rumble in the jungle WCW
Oh name a movie that had wrestlers that wasn't about wrestling. Okay. What is this? What am I Albert Einstein over the top?
All right. Well, you gave me the answer. All right. I'll be quiet robot streamer
Jesus, stop being a prison warden. Can you have can she have any secrets? No. Oh, but he's far with you robot streamer loves you man
I can't have anything to do around not even a thought
I forbid I have one coming.
Jamie's Cowboys just said I
look like Sylvester Stallone.
Thank you, Jamie. Thank you, baby.
Thank you very much, sweetie.
I know she's not.
I know that was a joke.
Say again, maybe thank you, Jamie.
I risked me and I risked
all this. That's over.
What?
Maybe an Irish stuff.
Get the fuck out of my house right now.
I will shove you, ginger bitch.
Get the fuck out of my house.
If you ever call me Irish, you better slow down your debts.
Irish snager.
That was too far.
You Irish sports snager.
You call me an asshole, you call me a piece of shit, that's one thing.
You call me Irish to learn.
Now you're fucked up.
Now you're fucking up.
All right, I got one better for you.
You're an American Schwarzenegger.
Oh, hey, come on.
Now you're trying to be silly and you're not.
Come on, stop it.
Yeah, I'm telling you, I'm much rather
an Arnold Schwarzenegger than a Schwarzenegger.
Oh, Jamie left you your joke, at least.
He wrote hot.
Yeah.
Well, say thank you.
Or he'd say thanks for playing with him by joke.
I would.
I just can't imagine that you go that I love Kim, but we went into her purse and I swear
The only thing we found was cookies and a slingshot like that's hardcore like that's fucking
I'm either hungry or I'm gonna shoot you in the eyes with a rock
He's fucking something else, man
So just show a little respect, okay
Jane these cowboys
You want a cigarette?
All right, let her show it here. Look at her.
And I'll tell you the truth and I mean this from my heart
This is probably the last time you're ever gonna seek him because I'm not letting people in my house that have no use
No, because this is no, you're not no
I'm not doing this. I'm not fuck. No. No, you are crazy enough. You know, you know
Psych psych
You remember a quarterback named Steve McNair. He was killed in his sleep by his girlfriend and she's not my girlfriend
He was killed in his sleep
I'm not going to sit here and get drunk.
If I were to kill you, I would have killed you already.
Wow, that's a compliment.
If I wanted to kill you, I would have killed you already.
That makes me feel a lot better.
That makes me feel so much better.
I would have been dead years ago.
Thank you.
That actually makes me feel really good.
That's how it should.
All right, can you get the hell out of my house right now?
I can make you feel better.
Take your knife and take your slingshot
and get the fuck out of my house.
Fuck you, fuck you with the night. No, it ain't games anymore. Keep your purse and get the fuck out of my house right now
Really? No, I'm not fucking with you. I'm not fucking with you because I will leave and shit. Why would you show me a knife though?
Why would you show me a fucking knife?
Because I've gotten stabbed in Baltimore and I carry it to protect myself
All right, but look at this look what I got my pocket
nothing. I tried to wink
like it's a knife. Like I
just didn't play along. S
to make a little show for
She's already trying to wonder how many organs
she can harvest from me.
Like, geez, Kim, leave my damn kidneys alone.
That's my kidneys, you're kidding.
You can go to the black market,
so I don't even know what's going on.
Oh, anybody would buy my kidney.
No, they wouldn't.
You're fucking kidding me.
Saidi, would you buy my kidney?
My kidney and liver are literally alcohol-soaked.
He said no, Saidi said no.
They're literally alcohol-soaked.
He was polite about it, though.
He just said no.
Like, no, Joe, come on.
They would.
Don't take mine either.
Well.
Lines are attacked, written in fucking smoke and hail.
That one time when I fucked you so deep,
I think I hit your organ, actually.
I think I hit your kidney.
Get the hell out of my house.
Get out.
He doesn't have an organ, he doesn't have an organ.
Yeah, do not fall asleep.
Thank you, Grim Reaper.
Leave my camera on for evidence.
Yes, thank you, Grim Reaper.
I do appreciate that.
Yup, that O's hat will be covered in blood and use its evidence and Gray Hughes investigations
is going to cover this.
Well, if you hear Baltimore Bits and that becomes a new thing like Florida Man, Baltimore
Bits goes crazy.
Well, take away the Baltimore and it's accurate.
No, Baltimore Bits goes crazy.
What about an Oregon grinder?
Oh, no, she don't like that.
Friends with benefits, hell no friends with benefits. She's gonna stab me. No, no
What's the opposite of benefits with the what's the word that is the opposite of a benefit?
Yep, she has a me